<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>hexagonal architecture on Carlos Buenosvinos</title><link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tags/hexagonal-architecture/</link><description>Recent content in hexagonal architecture on Carlos Buenosvinos</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 09:00:57 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tags/hexagonal-architecture/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Awesome two days helping @Lowpost_es team</title><link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/awesome-two-days-helping-lowpost_es-team/</link><pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 09:00:57 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/awesome-two-days-helping-lowpost_es-team/</guid><description>&lt;p>I have recently visited Valencia in order to help my friends at &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Lowpost&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->. It was great and I had a lot of fun! I would like to tell you a bit about how it was.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="who-is-lowpost">Who is Lowpost?&lt;/h3>
&lt;p>Lowpost is a cool start-up that are focused in Content Marketing. Lowpost connects companies that need interesting content with authors that can write about such topics. Authors bet for the open jobs and then they deliver the content to the final customer. Everything around such process is managed by the Lowpost platform.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>As a start-up, they have grown quite fast, so their code. They started with Drupal, as many start-ups, and then they added a Silex application. You know that testing is difficult, however, doing unit testing for Drupal is a challenge.&lt;/p>
&lt;h3 id="what-we-did">What we did?&lt;/h3></description></item><item><title>“Domain-Driven Design in PHP” (@dddbook) is finished</title><link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-in-php-book-is-finished/</link><pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-in-php-book-is-finished/</guid><description>&lt;p>Today, Keyvan, Christian and me are very happy to announce that &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->“Domain-Driven Design in PHP”&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> book is 100% complete. &lt;strong>380 pages&lt;/strong> and around &lt;strong>1400 readers&lt;/strong> so far.&lt;/p>
&lt;h4 id="thanks">Thanks&lt;/h4>
&lt;p>Thanks, thanks, thanks.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to everyone that has supported us in this project.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Christian&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>Keyvan&lt;/strong>. We don’t need words to understand each other.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to our &lt;strong>families&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>friends&lt;/strong>. Love is what you need to keep pushing.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Edd Mann&lt;/strong> for helping at the beginning with the language implementation details ;).&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Matthias Noback&lt;/strong> for his suggestions and his foreword.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Vaughn Vernon&lt;/strong> for being pragmatic and inspiring.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Ricard Clau, Albert Casademont, Victor Guardiola&lt;/strong> and &lt;strong>Jordi Abad&lt;/strong> for your contributions.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to &lt;strong>Natalye Childress&lt;/strong> for non stopping asking about uppercase or lowercase. With your work, the book can be read.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Thanks to everyone that committed fixes, you are great: &lt;strong>Jonathan Wondrusch, César Rodríguez, Yannick Voyer, Oriol González, Henry Snoek, Tom Jowitt, Sascha Schimke, Sven Herrmann, Daniel Abad, Luis Rovirosa, Luis Cordova, Raúl Ramos, Juan Maturana, Nil Portugués, Nikolay Zujev, Fernando Pradas, Raúl Araya, Neal Brooks, Hubert Béague, Aleksander Rekść, Sebastian Machuca, Nicolas Oelgart, and Marc Aube.&lt;/strong>&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>“Hexagonal Architecture with PHP” was published in phparch|magazine</title><link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/hexagonal-architecture-with-php-was-published-in-phparch-magazine/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2014 17:41:22 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/hexagonal-architecture-with-php-was-published-in-phparch-magazine/</guid><description>&lt;p>This week, the php|architect magazine has &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->published&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --> an article of mine about “Hexagonal Architecture with PHP”. Here’s the introduction:&lt;/p>
&lt;p>“With the rise of DDD (domain-driven development), architectures promoting domain-centric designs are becoming more popular. This is the case with &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Hexagonal Architecture&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->, also known as &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->Ports and Adapters&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted -->, that seems to have been rediscovered recently by PHP developers. Invented in 2005 by Alistair Cockburn, one of the Agile Manifesto authors, the Hexagonal Architecture allows an application to be equally driven by users, programs, automated tests, or batch scripts, while being developed and tested in isolation from its eventual run-time devices and databases. This results in infrastructure-agnostic web applications that are easier to test, write, and maintain. Let’s see how to apply it using real PHP examples.”&lt;/p>
&lt;p>I would like to share with you some thought, the cover and the code repository.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>