<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>value objects on Carlos Buenosvinos</title>
    <link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tags/value-objects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in value objects on Carlos Buenosvinos</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:00:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tags/value-objects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>“Domain-Driven Design in PHP” (@dddbook) is finished</title>
      <link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-in-php-book-is-finished/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Sep 2016 11:00:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-in-php-book-is-finished/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Today, Keyvan, Christian and me are very happy to announce that &lt;a href=&#34;https://leanpub.com/ddd-in-php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;#8220;Domain-Driven Design in PHP&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt; book is 100% complete. &lt;strong&gt;380 pages&lt;/strong&gt; and around &lt;strong&gt;1400 readers&lt;/strong&gt; so far.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&#34;thanks&#34;&gt;Thanks&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks, thanks, thanks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone that has supported us in this project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Christian&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Keyvan&lt;/strong&gt;. We don&amp;#8217;t need words to understand each other.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to our &lt;strong&gt;families&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;friends&lt;/strong&gt;. Love is what you need to keep pushing.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Edd Mann&lt;/strong&gt; for helping at the beginning with the language implementation details ;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Matthias Noback&lt;/strong&gt; for his suggestions and his foreword.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Vaughn Vernon&lt;/strong&gt; for being pragmatic and inspiring.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Ricard Clau, Albert Casademont, Victor Guardiola&lt;/strong&gt; and &lt;strong&gt;Jordi Abad&lt;/strong&gt; for your contributions.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to &lt;strong&gt;Natalye Childress&lt;/strong&gt; for non stopping asking about uppercase or lowercase. With your work, the book can be read.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to everyone that committed fixes, you are great: &lt;strong&gt;Jonathan Wondrusch, César Rodríguez, Yannick Voyer, Oriol González, Henry Snoek, Tom Jowitt, Sascha Schimke, Sven Herrmann, Daniel Abad, Luis Rovirosa, Luis Cordova, Raúl Ramos, Juan Maturana, Nil Portugués, Nikolay Zujev, Fernando Pradas, Raúl Araya, Neal Brooks, Hubert Béague, Aleksander Rekść, Sebastian Machuca, Nicolas Oelgart, and Marc Aube.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dot: Puzzles for smart masses</title>
      <link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/dot-puzzles-for-smart-masses/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 03:00:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/dot-puzzles-for-smart-masses/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have always been interested in games, just for fun, nothing serious. A game is IMHO the most difficult piece of software to write. Think for a second. It needs support for user input devices (mouse, keywords, gamepads, etc.), graphics (2D or 3D), sounds and music, physics, AI, networking when playing with more players and it has to perform really, really fast. That&amp;#8217;s not the typical PHP web, is it? Today, I would like to present my first really small and silly game, and probably the last one :) for iOS/Android and the technologies behind it. Hope you like it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Driven Design: Entities and Value Objects Webcast at @AtrapaloEng (Spanish)</title>
      <link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-entities-and-value-objects-webcast-at-atrapaloeng-spanish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Oct 2014 08:00:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/domain-driven-design-entities-and-value-objects-webcast-at-atrapaloeng-spanish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Siguiendo con las formaciones de DDD de Atrápalo, os dejo el video sobre Entities y Value Objects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tactical Domain-Driven Design Screencast at PHPBarcelona (Spanish)</title>
      <link>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tactical-domain-driven-design-screencast-at-phpbarcelona-spanish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2014 05:59:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://carlosbuenosvinos.com/tactical-domain-driven-design-screencast-at-phpbarcelona-spanish/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Os dejo el video sobre DDD Tactical Design que hice en la Monthly Talk de PHPBarcelona. Nos dio tiempo a charlar un poco de estrategia, ver los Value Objects, Entities y algo de Repositories. La charla está basada en el libro que Christian, Keyvan y yo estamos escribiendo en leanpub: &lt;a href=&#34;https://leanpub.com/ddd-in-php&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34;&gt;&amp;#8220;Domain-Driven Design with PHP by Examples&amp;#8221;&lt;/a&gt;. En los últimos 30 minutos hablo sobre cómo estamos gestionando la Integración Continua en Atrápalo.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>